http://www.zanewilliams.com/privacy-policy.html

Request Quote
Menu
CompanyCompany HistoryAwardsTestimonialsNewsProductsLight Pole BannersBanner BracketsPoly Canvas Light Pole BannersCustom BannersBow BannersTeardrop BannersCustom Printed PostersBacklit SignageArchitectural SignageTransit Advertising SignageTrade Show Displays & TableclothsFloor GraphicsWindow & Wall Decals & ClingsPoint Of Purchase Displays & KitsBanner StandsBanner FramesFlagsRexFramesCustom Wall PaperPromotionsSocial Distancing DecalsCapabilitiesDesign & PrepressPrintingDie Cutting & FinishingWarehouse & FulfillmentEquipmentGalleriesSaint Louis Science CenterSuper Graphics for WallsAll Star GameArmory BuildingCustom Signage & GraphicsFloor Graphics, Window Decals & ClingsLight Pole, Bow Banners & MoreSchool BannersCommunity FinancialMagic HouseHoliday BannersSubmit ArtworkArt RequirementsRequest QuoteContact
Privacy PolicyCompanyCompany HistoryAwardsTestimonialsNewsProductsLight Pole BannersBanner BracketsPoly Canvas Light Pole BannersCustom BannersBow BannersTeardrop BannersCustom Printed PostersBacklit SignageArchitectural SignageTransit Advertising SignageTrade Show Displays & TableclothsFloor GraphicsWindow & Wall Decals & ClingsPoint Of Purchase Displays & KitsBanner StandsBanner FramesFlagsRexFramesCustom Wall PaperPromotionsSocial Distancing DecalsCapabilitiesDesign & PrepressPrintingDie Cutting & FinishingWarehouse & FulfillmentEquipmentGalleriesSaint Louis Science CenterSuper Graphics for WallsAll Star GameArmory BuildingCustom Signage & GraphicsFloor Graphics, Window Decals & ClingsLight Pole, Bow Banners & MoreSchool BannersCommunity FinancialMagic HouseHoliday BannersSubmit ArtworkArt RequirementsRequest QuoteContact
Home > Privacy PolicyZane Williams Privacy PolicyWhat This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how Zane Williams treats personal information that Zane Williams collects and receives regarding information related to your use of Zane Williams products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
Information Collection and Use
Zane Williams collects personal information when you register with Zane Williams, when you use Zane Williams products or services, when you visit Zane Williams pages or the pages of certain Zane Williams partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Zane Williams may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
Zane Williams automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Zane Williams cookie information, and the page you request.
Zane Williams uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Computer configuration: We automatically receive and log information from your browser, including your IP address, your computer's name, your operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed.
Referral, clickstream and site interaction data: We may also record the URL you linked from to get to www.zanewilliams.com, your clickstream through and from our Web site, and other generally accepted tracking information.
E-mail delivery and open rates: To help us make our e-mails more useful and interesting, and to ensure that we are delivering the services you have ordered, we often receive a confirmation when you receive and/or open e-mail from Zane Williams.
Information from Other Sources
Customer and order data from our partners: If you registered directly with a business partner for which we provide fulfillment or other services, your account information and order information is passed to us.
Updated delivery and address information: We may obtain updated contact information from third parties in order to correct our records and fulfill your orders or deliver communications to you.
Demographic and purchase information: We may reference other sources of demographic and purchase information in order to provide you with more targeted communications and promotions.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Zane Williams does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: Trusted third parties: With your consent, we will make your Personal Information available to trusted third parties who offer products and services we think may be of interest to you so that you can receive information or opportunities related to those products and services. A trusted third party may use shared information in accordance with its own privacy policy; We transfer information about you if Zane Williams is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Zane Williams will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Messages required to service your Zane Williams account: Zane Williams may send newly registered users a welcoming e-mail, as well as messages confirming each event you register for at www.zanewilliams.com; confirming your account changes; inviting you to participate in customer surveys; and informing you of important product or service updates related to our core business.
Marketing messages about Zane Williams: We may send you marketing messages related to our services you receive.
Optional marketing messages from Zane Williams: Registered users may also occasionally receive information or special promotions from Zane Williams about additional services. You may update your preference with regard to receiving such messages by opting out in the footer of each e-mail.
Optional marketing messages from trusted third parties: With your consent, Zane Williams may share your Personal Information with trusted third parties so that you may receive information or opportunities from them about relevant products and services they offer. You may update your preference by opting out in the footer of each e-mail.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a Web site can store on your computer's hard drive. When you visit Zane Williams, create a user account, or otherwise interact with a Zane Williams event online, we may set cookies on your personal computer. We require that cookies be enabled in your Web browser so that we can identify you as a repeat visitor or customer and maintain session information for logged-in users. We also use cookies to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of our Web site. Zane Williams may allow other companies that are providing content on our site to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of cookies is subject to their respective privacy policies.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Zane Williams solution services, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Zane Williams Newsletter, that are considered part of your Zane Williams account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
"No Spyware" Policy
Zane Williams does not contain Spyware. Spyware is software that is installed deceptively to gather information about you without your knowledge. This can include centrally recording your personal Internet usage, monitoring your keyboard strokes or capturing personal information. If you think that you downloaded and/or installed spyware, we suggest reporting it on the alt. Privacy spyware newsgroup-available on all Google Groups.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Zane Williams may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your Zane Williams account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please use the following contact information:Zane Williams5757 Manchester RoadSt. Louis, MO 63110Toll Free:  800.395.2468Phone: 314.647.0787Fax:  314.647.0771
"We're Not Just Another Internet Banner Company"
What our clients are saying...
“I want to thank for all the work you did to make the MetroLink station look so great. Everyone is thrilled with the final product (hope you are too). Jeff, special thanks for your willingness to respond to our concerns about the windscreens by producing them again, differently. They look outstanding now. I'm sure the crowds coming down to the Riverfront for July 4th celebrations got the full impact of the station. Your efforts are very much appreciated.” - Susan
"All I can say (or anyone at the city hall) is OUTSTANDING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! THANK YOU SO MUCH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!"
-Lori
“You are the shining stars of the banner industry and the other vendors we have used in the past have become lackadaisical and unresponsive. I am requesting to the city that you become our only vendor for banners because of superior customer service.”
-Robb
"I just got off the phone with my client, and she is SOOO happy with how these turned out! She wanted to make sure that everyone who helped get these for them knows how much they appreciate the great work. I also wanted to let you know how nice it was working on this project with you guys - you made my life just that much less difficult, and that counts for a lot in my book :) Thank you!"
- Mary Ann
"You guys do a great job and someone from a neighboring town (Carbondale) came by and asked who does our banners, so I gave them your contact information!"
- Heather
“Appreciate the follow-up. I've been very pleased by the service and quality of your firm.”
- John, St. Louis Children’s Hospital
Newsletter Sign-Up
Email Address *
© 2020 Zane Williams   |   Web Design by Captiva Marketing
